

CONTACT

- +91 98212 74524
- New Delhi, India
- linktr.ee/anubhavsilas

HARD SKILLS

- · Guitar, Bass, Drums, Keyboard
- Logic Pro X
- Multitrack Recording
- Sample Manipulation
- Room Treatment
- Songwriting
- Microphone Techniques
- Scoring

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Active listening
- Teamwork

EDUCATION

AAFT, Noida

BA in Performing Arts (Music) Diploma in Music Production Completed in 2022

St. Columba's School, New Delhi

High School Completed in 2018

ANUBHAV SILAS

MUSIC EDUCATOR



ABOUT ME

Anubhav Silas is an independent artist based in New Delhi, India, with over 12 years of experience as a guitarist and 9 years as a music producer and composer. His recent work includes two singles, **Psalm 24** and **Sunshade**, along with his debut instrumental album, **Twenty Four Hours**, featuring five original compositions.

Anubhav has an extensive portfolio, having collaborated with various bands, Acappella groups, Christian ensembles, and has performed on radio stations alongside renowned artists. He has worked internationally with companies such as **GetGood Drums**, **JST**, and **Submission Audio** and is currently working under Triquetra Studio.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Music Producer and Composer

Triquetra Studio

2017 - PRESENT

- Produced and Composed 7 songs independently.
- Music Production and Composition for Kabeer Ali, Magnifiers, Cherubim, Abhishek Raj Masih, Theophany Gajpal, Anish Masih and United Worship.
- Lead Guitarist for Magnifiers, Tsabaoth and Kabeer Ali.
- Endorser for GetGood Drums, JST, and Submission Audio.

Music Teacher

Freelance

2017 - PRESENT

- Guitar and Vocal Tutor for more than 30 students.
- Music Counsellor for multiple leadership programs with LiveJam Break Free
 Tour at various reputed schools like Blue Bells Public School, Lotus Valley
 International School, Father Agnel School, Noida.



ACHIEVEMENTS

Grade 8 Guitar (Distinction) - Trinity College, London

Secured a position in the **Top 50 Guitarists** all across the world for Jared Dines **Best Guitarist** award for 4 successive years (2014 - 2017) in Delhi, India

More than 1 Lakh streams on Spotify

Honored for the **Best Band** for 3 consecutive years (2015 - 2017) in Delhi, India **13th position** in Beatboxing Competition in India

Received recognition in National newspapers

Over 10 million views on a beatboxing video on Instagram



ADDITIONAL WORK

Music Workshop Facilitator at St. Columba's, New Delhi

Music Judge for competitions at Amity Gurugram, VIPS, St. Thomas, Don Bosco